Unfortunately for me, Kosaku Kawajiri's
shoes are a little on the large side.
To avert suspicion, I have to gradually
swap them out with ones that actually fit.
Hayato.
No goodbye for your dad?
Have a good day at school.
What the?
Hurry!
Something horrible is lurking downstairs!
Oh, honey, it was utterly horrifying!
I thought I was going to die!
That was scary, but now I get to melt into
the rugged arms of the man of my dreams!
I love you so much, honey buddy!
Please, you have to get that
strange cat out of our basement
A cat
Meguru-yuku-ki-duki-ku-machi Miracles
out to be one of those adorable british
short hairs could you believe it it had
perfect proportions had those gorgeous
yellow eyes and velvety bluish gray fur
were to die for well aren't you just the
cutest now how did you get in here whoops
bad idea
he must have come in through
the window he's He's a cute little thing,
but he can't stay down here forever.
If I don't get him to scat, he
might pee on that potato sack.
Oh, and what if he has fleas?
Ah, all I have to do is avoid eye
contact and approach nice and slow.
I know what to do.
If I show him I'm not a threat,
I'm sure he'll let me get closer.
Look, Mr.
Kitty, I'm showing you my
belly and being submissive.
Let's be friends, what do you say?
Hang on.
Why am I begging for this cat's attention?
Time to scram, kitty.
You've more than outstayed your welcome.
Don't test me, cat.
Screw you!
Enough!
He was hanging on the ceiling
like some kind of furry bug.
As terrifying as that
was, it gets even scarier.
It's crazy, but when I saw its
neck, it had a gaping hole in it.
It was as big as a one-yen coin, and
then I heard something come out of it.
Really, a hole?
Curious, could it be a
wound from the arrow?
I swung the broom at him like a mad
woman before he finally ran away.
Please, can you go down
there and look around?
I'm scared out of my mind.
You said he had a gash in his throat?
Well, dear, what's going on down here?
Is the cat gone?
He is. Dead and gone. Huh?
What are you talking about?
Are those?
Shards of glass that
ripped through his body.
No, it can't be!
I was just trying to...
It was an accident.
No one's at fault.
Just bad luck.
No one did anything wrong.
Least of all you.
Apparently he had a gash in
his throat before the accident,
but now there's no telling
if he was a stand user.
No, he was just an ordinary cat.
Good morning, Mario.
There's nothing better than the
morning after a heavy rain, am I right?
I saw a beautiful rainbow
on my way to work.
I wonder if it's still there.
What is this place?
He thought to himself.
Why am I here?
Meow, meow.
Someone got me with an
arrow a couple of days ago,
but I thought I came
out of that scrap okay.
What?
My body is totally different.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why is it all weird now?
And why the hell am I stuck in the ground?
He meowed in panicked confusion.
Where in the world did
he bury him? Poor thing.
I'm so sorry, pretty kitty.
I hope you rest in peace.
Hmm, who is this strange
lady, he wondered.
I'm getting a real bad feeling about her.
The broom!
Now I remember.
This woman.
She was there when all that glass got stuck
in me and I wasn't able to move anymore.
I'm in this whole mess because
of that horrible woman, he fumed.
A flurry of confusion overcame him.
What was that, he thought?
Something just happened.
When I let my anger for that
lady out, she fell over in pain.
My toenail!
What the hell happened to it?
Oh no, it might be a curse.
Did I get it from that cat?
Having survived his entire life
by using his animal instincts,
he intuitively understood his
new power and how to use it.
The little bastard's a stand user.
But why is this thing growing where
I buried the stray cat last night?
And for that matter, what the hell is it?
What did it do to that sparrow?
I didn't catch a glimpse of its stand.
More importantly,
I need to somehow figure out whether
this thing poses a genuine threat to me.
Doesn't seem like it wants me dead.
But even so, to be on the safe
side, I'll have to prune it.
it fell asleep eating its prey is it a
type of plant or could it be an animal
eliminating it would be easy so i
have time for a little investigation
the way it innately
looked back at me when i
called it appeared almost
cat-like how strange
the way it seems compelled to sniff
my hand is also uniquely feline
it enjoys being petted as well
factoring that in with its
eerie purring it's acting
like a cat does before it
falls asleep but none of
that tells me whether it
harbors any ill will toward
me i have to know for sure
and there's only one way
well it's certainly angry but at the
very least now I know this thing doesn't
want to do me any harm there's no doubt
it's the cat I buried here yesterday so the
gouge in its throat
was from the arrow what
does it mean um honey
it's her I wouldn't
stand in that spot if I were you my The
toenail got ripped off right over there.
It's dangerous, dear.
I see.
The cat must have gotten
angry and attacked the woman,
if she ever found out this thing existed.
She'd run her big mouth
and gossip would eventually
spread to Jotaro Kujo and
his obnoxious cohorts.
I can't allow that to happen.
What are you doing?
That's where you buried the cat, right?
I don't like that spot.
It feels like it's cursed.
I buried the cat somewhere else.
Now please go back inside
and nurse your foot.
No, you're lying.
You're lying to protect me
from something, aren't you?
Shit, it looks like I was wrong.
This cat is gonna be nothing but trouble.
I may not know what its stand can do,
but I'll exterminate it nonetheless.
Deadly queen!
Sorry, but you're about to be uprooted.
Bob Type 1, switch on!
What the?
There's no way it could be a dud.
Which means this thing did it.
It must have anti-detonation abilities.
Is that a plant?
Why is it moving?
Didn't I just tell you to go inside?
Shinobu!
The moment that cat plant batted away
Deadly Queen's bomb, it exploded.
Could this thing's ability be?
As the creature saw the woman lying
unconscious, it thought, I'm going to kill her.
That's quite enough.
Your attack's on her end now.
You're about to disappear.
If he wants to get in the
way, then he dies too!
There's no other explanation.
The bomb failed to explode
because it was deprived of air.
The plant instinctively
knew how best to utilize
its newly acquired abilities
to kill its enemies.
Wait a minute.
Could it stand ability be to
control the air around it?
It's coming.
It fired something, but
I couldn't see what.
Deadly queen!
So it did shoot at us.
The little shit.
It's weaponizing masses of air.
Bastard!
I'll pound you into fertilizer!
What?
It's like I'm pressing
on an invisible balloon.
It really can manipulate the air.
What?
Damn it!
I can't see it,
but it must have released another
one of those compressed air bullets.
But where did that creature aim it?
What?
It hit the cactus!
Shinobu!
This doesn't make any sense.
Ushikaga Kira just feel a
sense of relief for this
woman because the cactus
needles missed her eyes?
What is this feeling?
Could I actually be
worried about someone else?
What am I thinking?
My only concern is what
might happen if this woman
dies and Jotaro Cujoh
discovers I'm at this house.
That's the only reason I'm
relieved to see that she's safe.
That's all there is to it.
Your air attack is now powerless.
Your projectiles might be invisible,
but I know how your tricks work.
You simply compress air and launch it at
your opponent in a
scattering of projectiles.
Now Deadly Queen knows how
to get around your attack.
What?
The little shit he
injected an air bubble into
my vein it's traveling
deeper into my body.
I'm not exactly a medical
expert but injecting
more than 10 cc's of any gas into a vein
can cause blood vessel
blockage and death and
I'm positive this is way
more than 10 cc's. No!
Damn, I can't get it out.
There's no other way.
I have to do it! Deadly Queen!
I underestimated that wretched weed.
It's power to control an attack with air.
It's more formidable than I imagined.
What do I do?
All right.
It's preparing to fire again!
Snake!
That was far too close.
I suppose I'll let it slide for now.
Its execution has been stayed.
Kosaku told me that he buried that
poor kitty far away from the house.
When I told him about the cat's curse,
he said it was just a figment of
my imagination brought on by fear,
and that I should get some rest.
I can't believe it.
I fainted right in front of him.
How embarrassing!
But he was nice enough to
stay home and look after me,
even though it made him late for work.
It was like a dream.
It felt like he understood
me for the first time ever.
This has been the most
blissful morning of my life.
Well, are you enjoying it?
Really, Hayato?
I can't believe that boy left
home without saying goodbye again.
That little brat!
Has he been watching me?
Oh no, sweetie?
You're eating from my plate!
I know how you hate shiitake mushrooms.
So I took them out.
What brought about this
sudden change of heart?
Wow, you've already eaten
more than half of mine?
But don't get me wrong.
I'm positively thrilled to
see you wolfing them down.
They're not so bad when you
give them a chance, are they?
Yeah.
All right, then.
I'm heading out.
I hope you have a good day, sweetie pie.
Oh, that's too bad.
A goodbye kiss would have been nice.
Although, I feel as though
we're closer than ever.
And before long, my seductive
love will overwhelm him.
He put his shoes on with a shoehorn.
And he was definitely wearing
25.5 centimeter size shoes.
Why does he have shoes that
are two different sizes?
Even weirder, mom and dad are
getting along better than ever.
And he scarfed down those mushrooms
even though he hates them.
This is all so bizarre.
Why in the world would he need to practice
writing his name over and over again?
And then there's what I
saw happen last night.
I kept replaying the footage,
but that's just a pot of dirt.
What could he be doing with that
much soil and a bag of cat food?
Then he goes into the closet
like everything's normal.
They're all wearing hats
is that part of their
dress code what is this i'm
getting a strange feeling
The attic
Whoa. Oh man. That's weird.
I wonder what that thing is.
Freaky.
It's way too dark in here.
I can't make it out.
There.
It's that bag.
Huh?
What?
That plant is moving!
No, that's not a plant.
It has eyes.
And it's looking right at me!
Hang on.
Could that bag of cat
food be for this creature?
I didn't expect you back then, Shantani.
Did you forget something?
Did you realize you left without
giving me a goodbye kiss? No.
Aw, then what is it?
I can get it for you if you want.
No, I'll do it myself.
Why the heck did he come back?
Oh no!
What did this plant do to me?
What are these weird things on me?
It's like I'm being strangled by some
kind of invisible inflatable shackles!
I'm being pinned to the
air by the air itself!
He's coming up the stairs!
I've gotta get free!
That came from the attic.
I knew that brat was up to something.
It hauled off and attacked me
when I tried to shut the window.
Does that mean it needs sunlight to move?
That's it.
If I'm being held by masses of air...
Awesome.
So the sunlight was fueling it.
That noise.
What's going on here?
Did the feral cat try to get its food from
the shelf and end up
spilling it on the floor?
I thought the lack of sunlight would
keep it calm for the time being.
But traces of light are
seeping in through the window.
Still, I thought Hayato may
have rummaged around up here.
But I guess I can chalk
that up to overthinking.
That said, had that little brat discovered
the truth about who I really am,
then I would have had no choice
but to put an end to his life.
somehow he's wearing my
dad's face but that's not my
dad who is that guy why is
he here what does he want
Stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you.
Oh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you,
but oh, I got to find you.
Oh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you,
but oh, I got to find you.
Let's rock out!